hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Krakowski and on this podcast I
help you grow in your life your business
to make more money if you're a coach
trainer Mentor or speaker these
strategies are going to work for you and
I'm going to talk about something today
that's been controversial I've had
people
not like when I talk about this shut me
down attack me things like that say that
it's unethical
Etc so realize that what I'm about to
share is very risky
um but it'll change your life in a
positive way if you actually apply it
what do I mean by that is total radical
self-acceptance
accepting yourself no matter what you do
and you can understand why some people
would see this as dangerous thinking
and think that
I should be put in prison for
recommending that you actually love
yourself and honor yourself even after
you make the biggest possible mistakes
possible and that you actually encourage
yourself and give yourself the most
self-compassion and the most self-love
when you mess up the hardest or when
things don't go how you wanted them to
or whatever
that when
you feel like oh I'm screwing up I'm
messing up that you actually say you
know what it's okay I'm human today and
this is part of my Human Experience
and and I'll tell you this it'll make
you a whole heck of a lot more money in
your business
to be radically self-accepting
of yourself and not feeling like I have
to be something else today in order to
succeed I have to become something I'm
not I have to pretend I have to fulfill
an obligation that somebody else has
placed on me I have to fill a role over
here because somebody has told me that I
have to do that and I have to prove and
validate that I'm good enough based on
how I perform and what I produce
and I want to eradicate that thinking
which
is in our culture and Society
everything at all level of society
tries to pressure you
into
doing everything perfect
holding yourself accountable which I
believe in self-accountability
but there's also a level of extreme
unnecessary and really
unhealthy quote unquote accountability
and let me explain what I mean by that
this is why this is controversial is
when every little thing that you do
you're just beating yourself up over
you're just constantly self-punishing
yourself it's this punishing level of of
accountability of okay I gotta I gotta
hurt myself now because I made a mistake
and that I have to I have to now work a
thousand times harder and make it harder
on myself to earn the right to be worthy
of success because I failed this one
time
or because I did this thing that I am
not proud of or I made this choice that
I'm not proud of you know I've made some
choices in my life I'm not proud of and
and they had consequences that I had to
suffer but I would challenge you
and this is
listen I believe in the rule of law and
criminals being put in jail for
doing bad things to people understand
that
I also believe that you need to get to a
place where you do not fear
consequences of your actions
and you're able to step out with
boldness
not walking timid and afraid of how
something might pan out
because of what you did that you just go
out there with
excitement Happiness joy and you don't
really worry you throw all caution to
the wind you recklessly
step into the next season in your life I
encourage this
often with my high level coaching
clients and this is one of the most
misunderstood things that people believe
that I'm sharing here's why is I came
from an extremely straight laced
um
hyper religious Christian background
where it was like
a cult and it wasn't healthy and so for
me I naturally gravitate towards
perfectionism a high level of
self-discipline getting a ton of stuff
done
and over stressing myself out to make
sure that I do all the things I need to
do
I will
beat myself up more than anybody else
will about what I'm not doing right in
my life and what I could be doing better
but but here's the thing
that can only help you so far and there
is some help in our lives from the inner
critic pointing out to us hey we should
do this we should be doing that that's
okay
but if it turns into Obsession around
what you're not doing good enough see
here's the thing I become obsessed with
the results of my clients and where I'm
headed and the vision for my life and
where God has called me and where I'm
headed to go I'm obsessed with that but
I cannot get obsessed with the
negativity
and the mistakes and trying to make them
all perfect
you just can't
it will bog you down it'll drain your
energy and you won't have any energy to
actually do the thing that you were
called to do and so if you're a coach if
you're a trainer if you're a mentor
I believe
that especially in your marketing
that especially for you to reach your
goals to make a half a million dollars a
year to make the kind of income that you
want to make you have to be willing to
put yourself out there
flippantly
without fear and worry of how things
could be taken or might go wrong or what
people might say to you the other thing
is this is
you know we need to have self-control
when it comes to our social media
to not be Doom scrolling all day we can
end up gaslighting ourselves
into believing a lie about ourselves my
brain
has done this to where I
even start criticizing myself as not
being good enough and accusing myself of
things that I never even did
literally false accusations that my
brain ends up telling me about oh
they're gonna think you did this they're
gonna think you're doing that they're
gonna and all these worst case scenarios
if you're somebody who operates at a
worst case scenario thinking
in your life and you're trying to reach
a goal those two things are going to be
in conflict with each other
and you're not going to be able to reach
that goal because you're going to be so
tethered and attached to preventing the
negativity from happening what ends up
happening really is becomes more like a
self-fulfilling prophecy where you
create the very thing that you feared
the most
to where the very thing that you
didn't want to happen
it happens
and then you wonder how did I get here
well you can either learn
or you can
keep moving forward
I don't believe in losing or being a
loser I believe that you can win or you
can learn
to do it better next time
and when you have that mindset from the
scientific
experimentation methodology to where
everything that you're doing is just an
experiment it's just an experiment on
how this audience is going to respond
this piece of content as an experiment
over here I'm just testing things out
just to see how they react
how they connect how they continue
forward
I'm just testing the waters all the time
to see
how Something's Gonna Go
and if you make this your mission to
just keep experimenting with the ideas
that you have and you don't take
yourself too seriously you don't take
your business too seriously I get it it
might be serious business but at the end
of the day have fun with it do the most
fun thing even if it seems silly spend
time doing what's fun give yourself
the grace to sleep to rest and I
understand we have different extenuating
circumstances especially if you have
kids I just had a newborn baby in
January and so my life has been shaken
up by that in the best of ways and the
most positive way and
now I've had to learn you know what
I don't have to be so critical of myself
in order to make sure that I do the
things that I need to do
that I can give myself the grace
to not have to take as much time to get
stuff done that
I I can drop some balls that's okay
I don't have to do everything that
everybody expects of me are you kidding
there's people right now if I did
everything that everybody wanted me to
do I would go crazy because I would not
have the capacity
to even come close to doing all the
things that everybody around me says
that I need to be doing and that I'm
doing wrong and all that and then my
brain ends up repeating in my brain the
criticism and it starts validating and
creating this
self-reinforcing mental Loop of you're
not good enough and you need to perform
better and do better and rise up to a
higher level in order to be worth
making the kind of money you want to
make
having dream clients and having the life
you want to live and this is a big fat
lie
foreign
that you have to be different and reach
a Next Level before you're ready to
experience all the amazing things that
are out there for you
you're qualified right now you have
everything inside of you right now to
make the kind of money that you want to
make in a coaching business and you do
not
have to
go to the next level or anything like
that now sure we enjoy a growth mindset
it's called The Grow Your Life podcast I
Believe in Us growing and changing and
transforming and as coaches that's what
we have an opportunity to help people
with but we can't be so Tethered to oh
I'm not where I want to be I'm not where
I should be I'm not where I should be
I'm not where I should be instead have
gratitude for where you're at right now
at this moment in time and say I'm right
where I need to be and start to believe
that and start to own that and start to
be thankful for where you're at right
now
start to be grateful for the situation
that you're in
and not be so focused on what you don't
have yet
what isn't we or what hasn't worked out
for years
what hasn't gone your way for years
and learning to
love yourself enough
to take care of yourself to get yourself
out of a fight or flight state to calm
your nervous system down
to be
joyful and give yourself more days and
more opportunities where you're thankful
and joyful and having a great time and
doing the things that you love
and starting to retrain your brain that
I am worthy of taking care of myself no
matter how I perform no matter what
level I'm at and so I want to encourage
you right now maybe you've been saying
listen once I reach this level then I'm
going to treat myself in this way I want
you to go treat yourself this week
I want you to go treat yourself this
weekend and watch how that's going to
change your thinking
watch how that's going to change what
you do in your life what your what your
day feels like
foreign
I'm so sad when I see people working
harder than they need to because they
feel like they have to perfectionism and
the amount of time that we invest making
everything perfect in our marketing what
matters the most is the sales copy and
that's words and there's no even
Graphics behind that
we can get so caught up in all this
irrelevant stuff in our marketing and
what needs to be done and what needs to
be accomplished in our business that we
miss out on the beautiful things that
are right in front of us that can
radically transform our life
if we just take it if we just do
something with it if we just move
forward with it and so I want to just
encourage you you don't have to wait
until a certain day or a certain moment
in time or that you reach a certain
level or that you get through a certain
breakthrough or that certain pieces line
up enough so that then you can finally
be worth the goals that you have go
after them
with Reckless abandon
have some fun
create an offer create a live event
create
some kind of a coaching offer that you
can sell to people
and start believing that you're worth
people buying from the amount of sales
that you can make in your business is
directly related to your own level of
self-esteem and self-belief that you
have yourself of I am worth making this
much money if you don't think that
you're worth people paying you that much
they're not gonna pay you anything
they're not going to give you any money
in your business
because people can smell the desperation
they can smell that you don't believe in
yourself and it repels the right people
because they don't want to work with an
insecure person and so again don't be
beating yourself up because you're now
acting like an insecure person things
like that realize you are more powerful
than you give yourself credit for and
start walking in that Authority and
start walking in that belief and start
believing that nothing is impossible for
you that everywhere that your feet go
greatness happens
and that you rise in the morning with
greatness every single day
and then go out there and go after it
now you might say listen that's a load
of phooey Jeremiah I got no evidence
that proves that well
have some faith on what you can't see
right now
step out in faith and do something that
maybe you've never done before I can
tell you this the system that we teach
the system on how to grow a coaching
business
Works produces multiple six-figure
results the only thing that's stopping
you is learning the system and applying
the work
and applying it and building a coaching
business because we get too stuck in our
head we get too caught up in our
thoughts
and we talk ourselves out of the very
thing that we feel called to do and so
listen I want to just encourage you
today if you feel called to build a
coaching business a mentoring business
jump into one of the live events that
we're doing I'm doing a couple this
month I'm hosting a five-day event May
8th through the 12th
and I truly truly believe
no matter where you're starting from
you can have six figure success in a
coaching business
but you're not if you don't believe in
yourself and you're not going to if you
don't believe it's possible for you
but I know it's it's so easy to make
that much money
I'm going after an eight-figure goal
because we have surpassed multiple six
figures so many times over already
listen I know that you can succeed don't
talk yourself out of it just because
maybe you weren't raised to talk this
way or maybe you think it's silly too
you can be successful and you can make
the kind of money that you want to make
and I'm excited to be here
for you to help you to guide you to
direct you
if you need help or guidance you can
always post on my YouTube channel any
questions that you have any comments
that you have and listen jump on the
waiting list
for my client growth accelerator
when we open the doors to the client
growth accelerator the group coaching
program I'd love to have you join us
and help you create the life and the
business that you've always dreamed of
grow your life everybody have a great
week and we'll talk soon have a good one